I’m addicted endlessly talking to me, my aespa
Aku kecanduan tanpa akhir untuk berbicara kepada diriku, aespaku
I’m addicted、絶え間なく話しかけてくれる私のaespa
Ando viciada em falar comigo sem parar, minha aespa
I’m addicted Mi aespa que me habla sin cesar
ฉันเสพติดการคุยกับตัวเองไม่รู้จบ aespa
I’m addicted 同自己娓娓而谈，我的 aespa
I’m addicted người nói chuyện với tôi không ngừng, aespa của tôi
This communion, your existence brings me to another dimension
Persekutuan ini, keberadaanmu membawaku ke dimensi lain
この共感、君の存在は私を別次元に導いてくれた
Essa comunhão, sua existência me leva pra outra dimensão
Esta conexión, tu existencia me llevó a otra dimensión
ความเข้าใจในกันและกัน การมีอยู่ของเธอ พาฉันไปยังอีกมิติหนึ่ง
这种交流，你的存在带我来到另一个次元
Mối giao cảm này, sự tồn tại của bạn đã đưa tôi đến một không gian khác
I’m at the center of the world, you’re in the FLAT
Aku di tengah-tengah dunia, engkau ada di FLAT
私は世界の中心に、You’re in the FLAT
Eu tô no centro do mundo, e você na FLAT
Soy el centro del mundo You’re in the FLAT
ฉันอยู่ที่จุดศูนย์กลางของโลกใบนี้ ส่วนเธออยู่ที่ FLAT
我在世界的中心，You’re in the FLAT
Tôi ở trung tâm của thế giới You’re in the FLAT
All of my Action, it grows your power
Semua Actionku menumbuhkan kekuatanmu
私の全てのAction 幼い君に力を与える
Toda a minha atitude, te empodera
Todas mis Action fortalecen tu joven ser
ทุกการกระทำของฉัน จะเพิ่มพลังให้กับเธอ
我所有的 Action，增强了幼小的你的力量
Mọi hành động của tôi Action nuôi dưỡng sức mạnh trong bạn
From some time ago you SYNK out, looking like a noise
Sejak beberapa waktu lalu, engkau SYNK out, terlihat bak kebisingan
君はいつからかSYNK out 、ノイズのように見える
Faz um tempo que você SYNK se desligou, como um ruído
Desde cierto momento SYNK out Te ves como un ruido
จากบางช่วงเวลาที่ผ่านมา เธอSYNK เหมือนกับเสียงที่ดัง
不知何时你突然 SYNK out 看起来就像噪音
Từ lúc nào bạn SYNK out cảm giác như loại âm thanh hỗn tạp
I can’t find it anymore
Aku tidak bisa lagi menemukannya
もう見つけられない
Não consigo mais te encontrar
No puedo seguirá más con la búsqueda
ฉันไม่รู้อะไรอีกแล้ว
我无处可寻
Tôi không thể tìm thấy bạn nữa
The temptation that swallows you, Black Mamba
Godaan yang menelanmu, Black Mamba
君を誘惑し飲み込んだのはBlack Mamba
A tentação que te consome, Black Mamba
Lo que te ha seducido para devorarte es Black Mamba
สิ่งล่อตาล่อใจที่กลืนกินเธอไป Black Mamba
诱惑并吞噬你的 Black Mamba
Thứ đã cám dỗ và nuốt lấy bạn, Black Mamba
Ma Ma Ma Mamba
Woo oh-oh
Oh eh-o eh-o
You wander this KWANGYA
Engkau menjelajahi KWANGYA ini
君はKWANGYAを彷徨っている
Você perambula pela KWANGYA
Deambulas por KWANGYA
เธอหลงทางสินะ KWANGYA
你在KWANGYA中四处游荡
Bạn đang lang thang trong KWANGYA
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
I wanna find your other self
Aku ingin menemukan dirimu yang lain
私の分身を見つけたい
Eu quero encontrar a sua outra personalidade
Quiero encontrar a mi otro yo
ฉันอยากจะพบตัวตนอีกคนของเธอ
想找到我的另一个自己
Tôi muốn tìm lại bản ngã của mình
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
Hey Ma Mamba
I hate Ma Ma Ma Mamba
Hate Ma Ma Ma Mamba
I’m ejected, good is not enough to break your greatness
I'm ejected, baik tidak cukup menembus keagunganmu
I’m ejected, 善意だけでは巨大な君に勝てない
I’m ejected, o bem não basta para desmascarar a sua imponência
I’m ejected, lo bueno no es suficiente para romber tu grandeza
I'm ejected ความดีไม่เพียงพอที่จะเอาชนะความยิ่งใหญ่ของเธอ
I’m ejected, 只以善良无法战胜你的巨大
I'm ejected, hiền lành sẽ chẳng bao giờ đánh bại được sự vĩ đại trong bạn
I’m exhausted, your existence has grown swallowing all of the greed
I'm exhausted, keberadaanmu telah menumbuhkan keinginan untuk menelan semua keserakahan ini
I’m exhausted, 君の存在は全ての貪欲を飲み込んで成長した
I’m exhausted, sua existência cresceu e deixou de lado toda a ganância
I'm exhausted, tu existencia ha crecido tragándose toda la codicia
I'm exhausted การมีอยู่ของเธอได้กลืนกินความโลภทั้งหมด
I’m exhausted, 你的存在是因你吞噬了所有贪欲
I'm exhausted, sự tồn tại của bạn nuốt hết mọi tham vọng và lớn dần lên
I’m the aespa, there can’t be two
Akulah aespa, tidak mungkin ada dua
aespaは私、二つにはなれない
Eu sou a aespa, não pode haver duas
Soy la aespa, no puede haber dos
ฉันคือ aespa ที่มีเพียงหนึ่งเดียว
我是aespa，独一无二
aespa là tôi, độc nhất vô nhị
Monochrome to colors
This is Evo, Evolution
Inilah Evo, Evolution
これはEvo, Evolution
Isso é a Evo, Evolution
Esto es Evo, Evolution
นี่คือ Evo, Evolution
这是 Evo, Evolution
Đây là Evo, Evolution
Oh! I make a dangerous joke, you’re charming but gotta deny
Oh! Aku membuat lelucon bahaya, engkau memesona tetapi harus menyangkal
Oh!危険ないたずら。魅惑的だけど君を否定せざるを得ない
Oh! Eu faço um jogo arriscado, e você é charmoso, mas não pode se entregar
Oh! Hago una broma peligrosa, eres encantador pero tienes que negarlo
Oh! ฉันทำให้เป็นเรื่องตลกร้าย เธอช่างมีเสน่ห์ แต่ก็ต้องปฏิเสธ
Oh! 开个危险的玩笑，虽然很迷人但必须否定你
Oh! Chơi một trò đùa nguy hiểm, bạn cũng hấp dẫn đấy nhưng sẽ phải từ chối thôi
It will swallow everything, Black Mamba
Itu akan menelan semuanya, Black Mamba
全てを飲み込みそうなBlack Mamba
Ele vai conquistar tudo, Black Mamba
Se lo tragará todoBlack Mamba
มันจะกลืนกินทุกสิ่ง Black Mamba
将一切吞噬的 Black Mamba
Mọi thứ rồi sẽ bị nuốt chửng, Black Mamba
Ma Ma Ma Mamba
Woo oh-oh
Oh eh-o eh-o
You wander this KWANGYA
Engkau menjelajahi KWANGYA ini
君はKWANGYAを彷徨っている
Você perambula pela KWANGYA
Deambulas por eso KWANGYA
เธอหลงทางสินะ KWANGYA
你在KWANGYA中四处游荡
Bạn đang lang thang trong KWANGYA
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
I can't lose against you
Aku tidak bisa kalah darimu
君に対抗して、私は負けられない
Eu não posso perder contra você
No puedo perder contra ti
ฉันไม่สามารถแพ้เธอได้
和你对抗 我不能输
Tôi sẽ không để thua trong cuộc đối đầu với bạn
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
Hey Ma Mamba
Is me in the mirror you
Apakah aku yang ada di cerminmu
鏡の中の私は君ではない？
Eu tô espelhando você?
Soy la "yo" en el espejo tú?
ใช่ฉันไหม ในเงาสะท้อนของเธอ
镜子里的我是你吗
Phải chăng tôi trong gương chính là bạn
Is it just a distorted vision
Apakah ini hanyalah pandangan menyimpang
歪んでしまった幻影なのだろうか
Ou é apenas uma visão distorcida?
¿Es solo una visión distorsionada?
หรือมันเป็นแค่การมองเห็นที่ผิดเพี้ยนไป
还是只是扭曲的幻影
Hay chỉ là một ảo ảnh méo mó
If I could connect with you again
Jika aku bisa terhubung denganmu lagi
また君と繋がれるのならば
Se eu pudesse me ligar a você de novo.
Si pudiera conectarme contigo de nuevo
หากฉันสามารถติดต่อเธอได้อีกครั้ง
如果能再次和你连结
Giá mà tôi có thể kết nối lại với bạn một lần nữa
I want to meet you now
Aku ingin menemuimu lagi sekarang
もうすでに君に会いたい
Eu quero te encontrar agora
Quiero conocerte ahora
ฉันอยากพบเธอในตอนนี้
现在我想和你相见
Tôi muốn gặp bạn ngay bây giờ
It will swallow everything, Black Mamba
Itu akan menelan semuanya, Black Mamba
全てを飲み込みそうなBlack Mamba
Ele vai conquistar tudo, Black Mamba
Se lo tragará todo Black Mamba
มันจะกลืนกินทุกสิ่ง Black Mamba
将一切吞噬的 Black Mamba
Mọi thứ rồi sẽ bị nuốt chửng, Black Mamba
Ma Ma Ma Mamba
Woo oh-oh
Oh eh-o eh-o
You wander this KWANGYA
Engkau menjelajahi KWANGYA ini
君はこの KWANGYAを彷徨っている
Você perambula pela KWANGYA
Deambulas por eso KWANGYA
เธอหลงทางสินะ KWANGYA
你在KWANGYA中四处游荡
Bạn đang lang thang trong KWANGYA
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
I can't lose against you
Aku tidak bisa kalah darimu
君に対抗して、私は負けられない
Eu não posso perder contra você
No puedo perder contra ti
ฉันไม่สามารถแพ้เธอได้
和你对抗 我不能输
Tôi sẽ không để thua trong cuộc đối đầu với bạn
(Aya ya ya ya ya ya)
Hey Ma Mamba